https://triz-journal.com/privacy-policy/

What is TRIZ
Who Will Use TRIZ?
Contact us
NavigationSelect a Page:
What is TRIZ
Who Will Use TRIZ?
Privacy Policy
The TRIZ Journal values the protection of your personal information.  The TRIZ Journal also believes that you should be able to choose how The TRIZ Journal discloses and uses your personal information.  Please read this policy before visiting the The TRIZ Journal website or before providing any personal information to The TRIZ Journal.
Privacy Notice.
The purpose of this Privacy Notice is to explain The TRIZ Journal uses the information The TRIZ Journal collects about you, and how you may notify The TRIZ Journal of your choices in regards to how The TRIZ Journal uses that information.  The TRIZ Journal believes it is important to let you know how information about you is used and protected.  The TRIZ Journal is committed to the protection of the information you share with us and The TRIZ Journal will never collect any personal information (for example, your name and email address) about you without you knowingly providing it.
Collecting Personal Information.
You may generally visit The TRIZ Journal website without providing personal information.  The TRIZ Journal does collect the IP addresses and domain names of visitors for site administration purposes.  No personal information is obtained through an IP address.  The TRIZ Journal may share statistical or collected non-personal information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties.  This data is used to customize our website content and advertising to deliver a better experience to our users.
Some of the information collected is required for membership or business engagement purposes.  The type of personal information that The TRIZ Journal may collect could include, but not limited to, the following
Your name, address, phone and email contact information
Information about your employment such as employer name, title, address, and the industry of your employer
Use of Personal Information.
Unless otherwise stated, personal information provided by users will be used for marketing and promotional purposes only by The TRIZ Journal.
The TRIZ Journal collects personal information for the following purposes:
To determine membership eligibility and enroll a member in The TRIZ Journal
To provide you with products or services that you have requested
To communicate with you
To develop a membership directory
To administer The TRIZ Journal website
To process your payment for The TRIZ Journal products
The TRIZ Journal reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party, if legally necessary, required or authorized.  The TRIZ Journal also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, merger, or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of The TRIZ Journal, in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party.
Access to Personal Information. Members may correct or update personal information by logging into their account and clicking on “Manage My Account.”
PROTECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, The TRIZ Journal has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information The TRIZ Journal collects online.  Please understand, however, that while we try our best to safeguard your personal information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
You need to help protect the privacy of your own information, including maintaining the confidentiality of any account information or access credentials.  You must take precautions to protect the security of any personally identifiable information that you may transmit over any public or untrusted network by using encryption and other techniques to prevent unauthorized persons from intercepting or receiving any of your personally identifiable information.  You are responsible for the security of your information when using unencrypted, open access, public or otherwise unsecured networks.
Cookies.
A cookie is a small file placed on your computer when you visit a website.  The TRIZ Journal uses cookies to manage the website and email programs.  The TRIZ Journal does not use cookies to collect or store personal information.  Cookies are used to store non personal information to manage your website experience such as your type of web browser.  A cookie can also store preference information to customize your website experience.  Cookies help The TRIZ Journal understand how visitors and members use The TRIZ Journal website and emails so The TRIZ Journal can design better services in the future.
You can configure most Web browsers to notify you when cookies arrive and can either ask your approval to accept them, or be set to refuse cookies outright.  Most browsers also let you delete cookies you may have accepted in the past.
The TRIZ Journal occasionally uses cookies to display ads on sites across the Internet.  The TRIZ Journal and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to The TRIZ Journal website.  Any information that these third parties collect via cookies is not linked to any personal information collected by us.
Credit Card Information and Security.
The TRIZ Journal is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, customers and visitors.  The TRIZ Journal collects credit card information, such as your card number and card expiration date, when you purchase products on The TRIZ Journal website.  If you use a credit card to pay for any products or services of The TRIZ Journal, we may retain your credit card information in order to renew your account in the event you elect to renew your subscription.  The TRIZ Journal website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  The TRIZ Journal uses a secure server to transmit sensitive data to and from The TRIZ Journal website.  All data (including your credit card information) transmitted through our secure Web server is encrypted so no one else can read it.
Links to Other Websites.
The TRIZ Journal website may contain links to other sites.  These sites are not controlled by The TRIZ Journal and The TRIZ Journal is not responsible for any content contained on any such website.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites, and the privacy practices employed by such sites may not be the same as The TRIZ Journal’s practices.
The TRIZ Journal Website and Terms of Use.
Please refer to The TRIZ Journal’s Terms of Use on all issues related to accessing, posting and sharing information through The TRIZ Journal website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy.
From time to time, The TRIZ Journal may update its Privacy Policy.  The TRIZ Journal will post the new Policy with a new effective date to notify you of these changes.  By accessing and using The TRIZ Journal website after the effective date, you consent to the current Privacy Policy.
Customer Preferences.
If you wish to change or alter the information The TRIZ Journal has on file for you (for example your postal address or email address), if you wish to no longer be contacted by The TRIZ Journal, or if you prefer that we do not disclose information about you (other than disclosures permitted or required by law) you may notify us at any time by contacting The TRIZ Journal.
IMPORTANT: When contacting The TRIZ Journal, please be sure to include your first and last name, your address, your email address, and your phone number so The TRIZ Journal can accurately update your information or process your opt out request effectively.
If you have any questions or concerns, please Contact Us.
This policy is effective as of May 2, 2016.
About us
Mission, Vision & Values
Editorial Community
© 2019, The TRIZ Journal, all rights reserved.
